ezibuy.com.au 2015-04-27

# Privacy Policy - EziBuy Australia

We have put in place the following policy to protect your personal information. By using our website and/or providing information to us, you consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this policy.

In this policy, "personal information" means information about an identifiable individual.

**What personal information do we collect?**

You may give us personal information about yourself, such as your name, address, email address, credit card details and telephone numbers, when, for example, you become an EziBuy member, request a catalogue or make a purchase from us. If you do not give this information, we may not be able to provide goods or services to you.

When you visit our website we may collect more personal information, such as the address of your Internet service provider, the name of the web page directing you, and your clicks and activity on our site.

**Remarketing with Google Analytics and others**

We use Remarketing through Google Analytics and other third party providers to advertise online by delivering EziBuy ad content to you which is specifically targeted to your interests based on your visits to our website. Third-party vendors, including Google and Bazaarvoice, show EziBuy ads on sites across the Internet. Please see the Cookies section below for further information.

EziBuy website visitors who wish to opt out of Google Analytics or Bazaarvoice for Display Advertisers and/or customized Display Network ads can do so by visiting Google's [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb) or Bazaarvoice's opt-out mechanisms (the [NAI opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRonu67JcO%252FhmjTEU5z16ewqXqS%252Bgokz2EFye%252BLIHETpodcMTcJlNbnYDBceEJhqyQJxPr3NKNgNytJ5RhDlDA%253D%253D) or the [DAA opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRonu67JcO%252FhmjTEU5z16ewqXqS%252Bgokz2EFye%252BLIHETpodcMTcJlNbnYDBceEJhqyQJxPr3NKNgNytJ5RhDlDA%253D%253D)). You can also download the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**How do we use the personal information?**

We may use your personal information to process your transactions, to administer your account, to conduct credit and other checks, for our own internal purposes (such as risk management, staff training and billing), to facilitate our online services (including to provide the services contemplated by our Website Acceptable Use Policy), to help us to develop our website to be more available and user friendly to our customers, and for any other use associated with such purposes or which you may authorise.

In addition, we may use your personal information to promote and market our products and services, or the products and services of others. However, we will not do this by email or text (except as part of an email which facilitates, completes or confirms a transaction with you) unless we have your express, inferred or deemed consent to do so. These emails and texts will always include an "unsubscribe" facility. (for further details on how to unsubscribe see below).

Some uses of your personal information may involve the transfer of that information outside Australia, to be held and used by our related companies and business partners.

**Will we disclose your personal information to others?**

We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others without your consent.

However, we do use other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf, such as delivering packages, sending mail and emails, credit checking and processing payments. They will have access to your personal information needed to perform and provide these services, but we will not authorise them to use your personal information for other purposes. 

We also disclose (including by transfer to another country) your personal information to our related companies and business partners, such as financial services or insurance companies, for them to offer products and services to you. This information may include scrambled credit card details, although these will only be used with your consent for any transactions with them. If you do not wish your personal information to be disclosed, call us on 1800 148 148 or email us at [mail@ezibuy.com.au](mailto:mail@ezibuy.co.nz).

In addition, we may provide statistics with personal identifiers removed about our customers, readers, sales, traffic patterns and related site functions to reputable third parties. We may use service providers to assist us to aggregate and anonymise such information, so that it does not include any information from which an individual can be identified. We do not consider such aggregated and anonymised information to be personal information and its use is not subject to this policy.

We may also disclose your personal information where such disclosure is required by law.

**Cookies**

Our website uses a technology called cookies. A cookie is a small element of data that our website may send to your computer. Any such cookie is typically stored on your computer's hard drive and permits our website to recognise you when you return. Our use of cookies helps us to provide you with a better experience during your use of our website by allowing us to understand what areas of the site are of interest to you. You may configure your web browser to not accept cookies, although you may experience a loss of functionality as a result.

Reputable third party vendors, including Google and Bazaarvoice, show advertisements for our products on various sites on the internet. EziBuy and third-party vendors, including Google and Bazaarvoice, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

If you would like to opt out of the use of cookies for this purpose, please visit Google's [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb) (and select Opt Out from the left hand menu and follow the prompts) or [Bazaarvoice's NAI opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRonu67JcO%252FhmjTEU5z16ewqXqS%252Bgokz2EFye%252BLIHETpodcMTcJlNbnYDBceEJhqyQJxPr3NKNgNytJ5RhDlDA%253D%253D) or [DAA opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRonu67JcO%252FhmjTEU5z16ewqXqS%252Bgokz2EFye%252BLIHETpodcMTcJlNbnYDBceEJhqyQJxPr3NKNgNytJ5RhDlDA%253D%253D).

**Security**

We take security seriously, and have taken steps to ensure your personal information is secure. We use secure servers, and industry standard data encryption whenever we are receiving or transferring your personal information online. However, we accept no responsibility for any loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration or destruction of personal information which you submit to us.

**What about links to other websites?**

Our website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites may use cookies.  It is the responsibility of those third parties to collect appropriate consents from you in order to permit their own cookies (to the extent this is required by law) and to inform you about the cookies they use.  You should check the privacy policy on all third party websites to ensure you are comfortable with third party cookies (Bazaarvoice's privacy policy can be found here: [Bazaarvoice Privacy Policy](http://go.bazaarvoice.com/848PGD1740001Ct008Iq800 "Bazaarvoice Privacy Policy")). We have no responsibility for linked websites, and provide them solely for your information and convenience.  We specifically disclaim responsibility for their content, privacy practices and terms of use, and we make no endorsements, representations or warranties about their accuracy, content or thoroughness.  Your disclosure of personal information to third party websites is at your own risk.   

**Email, text and telephone communications**

You can subscribe to promotional and marketing email and/or text communications by registering for My EziBuy [here](https://www.ezibuy.com.au/default.aspx?Z=C&rnd=F3104821-57FF-4014-B7DE-D7BE2FB84EBA&action=displayaccount). The box to subscribe for email communications will be pre-ticked. If you are registering for My EziBuy and do not wish to receive email communications please remember to un-check this box. If you wish to subscribe for text communications, tick the "Text" box.

By subscribing to our email and/or text communications, or otherwise providing us with your email address and/or mobile number, you consent to receiving emails and/or texts (as the case may be) which promote and market our products and services, or the products and services of others, from time to time.

You can unsubscribe from our email communications at any time by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in any promotional or marketing email received from us or by signing into My EziBuy [here](http://www.ezibuy.com.au/) and unchecking "I want to receive: Email" box or by calling us on 1800 148 148 or emailing us at mail@ezibuy.com.au.

You can unsubscribe from our text communications at any time by following the directions to unsubscribe in any promotional or marketing text received from us or by signing into My EziBuy [here](http://www.ezibuy.com.au/) and unchecking "I want to receive: Texts" box or by calling us on 1800 148 148 or emailing us at mail@ezibuy.com.au.

Once you have unsubscribed from our email or text communications, we will remove you from the corresponding marketing list as soon as is reasonably practicable.

We use email open and click tracking including cookies, a single pixel image for tracking and link redirects for tracking clicks, for us to get a better understanding of which email communications are of most interest to you so we can provide you with a better experience by sending relevant and interesting email communications.

If you have any concerns or complaints regarding emails or texts received from us, for example if you are receiving unwanted emails or texts or are not the intended recipient, please call us on 1800 148 148 or email us at mail@ezibuy.com.au.

Calls may be monitored or recorded for training and quality control purposes.

**Updating your personal information**

You may obtain confirmation from us as to whether or not we hold personal information about you. You may also request access to or a copy of the information and/or request that corrections or changes are made to it. You can make changes to your personal information on our website, by calling us on 1800 148 148 or by emailing us at [mail@ezibuy.com.au](mailto:mail@ezibuy.co.nz).

**Policy changes**

We may review this policy from time to time and will notify you of any changes by posting an updated version on our website. Your use of our website following any updates constitutes acceptance of this policy as amended. We recommend you regularly review the policy when you visit our website. This document represents our privacy policy as at 1 November 2013.

**Feedback**

We welcome your questions and comments about privacy at EziBuy. Please call us on 1800 148 148 or email us at [mail@ezibuy.com.au](mailto:mail@ezibuy.co.nz).

[  
](mailto:mail@ezibuy.co.nz)EziBuy is part of the Data Warranty Register, a self-regulatory system under the governance of the Marketing Association that provides best-practice transparency relating to the collection, storage and use of marketing data by businesses.
